I watched last night's Game of Thrones
instead of writing the blog post I was
supposed to write and wrote this instead
I am Tyrion I see what others do not our
army of the Dead is climate change
it feels insurmountable and is growing
every day our dragonglass is truth and
connection we must stop uselessly
fighting one another and turn all of
that energy towards our collective
problems or we are going to be left
fighting over the scraps after the
apocalypse there is not one single hero
who can come and save us it's going to
take tens of thousands of us being
ourselves doing what we can do and
failing in the right direction
learning improving and working towards
solutions together we cannot stay in the
Crypt waiting for our government or
corporations to save us or we will die
here of our own ignorance and inaction
we are facing extinction and the longer
we wait the harder it is we can create
the technology that gives us the truth
we can make science politics history and
economics accessible and available to
every human being on this planet in a
way that we trust because we created it
together transparently you do not need
to be born a king or even to know your
lineage you can be a bastard and have a
real impact on the revolution that is
coming you do not need to be rich have a
university degree be charismatic or any
other improvement on your current self
you are perfect exactly as you are now
love for yourself love for others
exactly as they are right now in this
moment making community accessible to
every single human is how we wield love
for the revolution we are worthy of love
and connection we are all worthy of love
and connection and with the right
platform we can make it much easier to
find the people we resonate with and to
create a space where every individual
can be seen and heard for who they are
now there is space for everyone
people will come from everywhere when we
stop fighting each other because we are
different we can start seeing that our
diversity makes us stronger and better
our differences are what will save us
like brand sitting in the god wood being
the biggest
threat to the night king sitting with
ourselves feeling and healing our pain
is the biggest threat to our current
system and the most powerful thing that
we can do we can even make this process
easier for anyone who is willing it is
not only our talents and strengths that
will save us it is our full human selves
our challenges our shadow and our light
altogether it gives each of us a unique
position to see from and offer to each
other and the world we are not in
competition when enough of us can see
the true beauty in our diversity we can
create a space where anyone and everyone
can come together because we are strong
together
we are unstoppable together when we join
in cooperation we can do it all
peacefully and easily we only need to
create the tools and harness what is
already here no one Andre can back is
coming to save us we must mine the
dragonglass ourselves create the tools
that give us the truth so we can wield
that knowledge together against the
evils of greed that thrive in our
ignorance that has taken over our
society we can create the system of
cooperation where anyone can join
everyone is invited and nobody has to
lay down their life or give up their
freedom we can create a world of
abundance and peace for everybody a
world designed with and for our true
diversity a world designed for everyone
we are going to do so by creating a
global technology cooperative that is
run with complete transparency and
liquid democracy and we are going to use
it to create the tools we need to
understand the vast problems before us
and create solutions that work we are
going to make it fun easy and accessible
a better world for everybody is on its
way but we cannot wait in the crypt for
heroes to save us we must save ourselves
please like and subscribe and let's save
the world together
[Music]